opinion leaders express explicit
desires of violence directed at a dera
presidential candidate Some will
Consider these criteria inappropriate to
Perhaps Trump's entire deed should be considered
and political impropriety to call
Hillary Clinton for Crooked Hillary and
chanting lock her up is certainly both
clumsy and undignified but it's not
glorification of violence. To call Biden for
sleepy joe is mean but not even
battle between good and evil instead
to discuss matters of fact is one
deliberate democratic electoral strategy which
developed by election strategy Alexandro
verdin verdin led the election campaign he